survivalistboards.com 2017-06-06

# Survivalist Forum - FAQ: Privacy

**_Copyright Information_** :

No information on this site my be reproduced without the written consent of the owner or copyright holder of the material. 

By posting on this forum, members grant Kevin Felts non-exclusive rights to publish the material on survivalistboards.com.

The content on the SurvivalistBoards Website, except all user submissions, copyright Kevin Felts, 2006 - 2010

**_Disclaimer_** :

Kevin Felts (the owner of this site) does not engage in the practice of medicine or law. Under no circumstances does Kevin recommend particular treatments for specific individuals, or legal advice. In all cases, Kevin recommends that you consult your physician before pursuing any course of treatment or a lawyer for real legal advice.

Use any information gained on this site at your own risk.

**_Privacy Policy_** :

 _Introduction_

Kevin operates several websites including survivalistboards.com, survivalboards.com, survivalforum.us and elgms.com. It is Kevins policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

 _Website Visitors_

Like most website operators, Kevin collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Kevins’ purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how visitors use this website. From time to time, Kevin may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Kevin also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Kevin does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

 _  
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information_

Kevin may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, Kevin may monitor the most popular parts of the survivalboards.com. Kevin may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Kevin does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

 _  
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information_

Kevin discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that

(i) need to know that information in order to process it on Kevins’ behalf or to provide services available at Kevins websites, and

(ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Kevins websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Kevin will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Kevin discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Kevin believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Kevin, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of a Kevins website and have supplied your email address, Kevin may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Kevin and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Kevin takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

 _Cookies_

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Kevin uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of Survival Boards website, and their website access preferences. Kevins visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Survival Boards website, with the drawback that certain features of of the website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 _Privacy Policy Changes_

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Kevin reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Kevin – the owner of Survivalist Boards encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

 _ **Disclosure**_  
Survivalistboards.com contains advertising and some contextual affiliate marketing links, meaning we may get commission on sales of those products or services mentioned...The content of posts on this forum are never influenced by advertisers or an affiliate partnership, nor are posts written for the sole purpose of promoting a product. _ **FTC Required Disclosure**_

The Federal Trade Commission (FTC) now requires bloggers to disclose their relationship with companies, and individuals selling products. Whether the blogger received a payment for the product, whether the results are going to be typical,,,, just all kinds of stuff.

Since I’am not a lawyer, this is my attempt at such a disclosure.

I (Kevin) do not receive payments of any kind to review a product, if I did receive a payment it would be disclosed on a per-review basis.

Sometimes people will send me products to review. This does not influence my opinion of the product in anyway.

When I review a product – it needs to be noted that my results and opinion might differ from other peoples. Difference in manufacturing standards, quality control, and other factors out of my control might have an impact on the final product. Just because I have a product of a certain quality, does not mean that yours will be “exactly” the same.
